

ARTEM BLOSCHINSKY

Objective: looking for trainee/junior front-end developer vacancy

CONTACTS

- ☼ Dnipro, Ukraine.
- & Tel. +380 93 726-28-35
- 3 artem.artphoto
- dev.byartem.com
- github.com/bloschinsky

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH intermediate / B1

POLISH elementary / A1

UKRAINIAN / RUSSIAN native

SKILL

Main technical:

HTML5 / CSS3

Bootstrap / Materialize

JavaScript (ES5 / ES6)

jQuery

AngularJS

Experience with:

LESS, Jade/Pug, Git,

Node.js, Npm, Gulp

Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text

Design tools:

PhotoShop, Lightroom

Sketch app, Illustrator

Additional:

Teamwork

Team Management

Project Management

Problem solving

ABOUT ME



I was born in Dnipro, 32 years' old, not married.

Over 10 years' of working experience in different business areas, such as: foodstuff, hard-truck transport logistics, photography, design, digital printing. Have a practical understanding of business needs within B2B and B2C fields. Teamwork experience in such countries as Poland, Greece, Moldova & Russia.

My hobbies are photography, traveling by car, cycling, post crossing. I have B category driving license, strong driving skills, and long term opened Schengen visa.

WORK EXPERIENCE



FREELANCE TEAM / trainee front-end developer

UKRAINE / 2017

Make part of landing page layout, implement scripts and work with youtube api, fix bugs. Used technologies: native HTML, CSS & JS, Bootstrap, jQuery, youtube api.

PP KUCHMENKO / Purchase & transportation deputy director KAMENEC-PODOLSKY / FEBRUARY 2012 - MAY 2016

Work with suppliers, selection and organization of the goods delivery, quality control, problem solving, transport & logistics management, quality control of vehicles and drivers.

SELF EMPLOYED / Photographer

UKRAINE / SEPTEMBER 2009 - PRESENT TIME

Photo shooting, photo editing, promotion, work with clients.

RASTUDIO / prepress, designer, retoucher.

DNIPRO / SEPTEMBER 2003 - SEPTEMBER 2009

Work with customers, preparation photographs for large-format printing, photographic design, retouching and restoration of photographs.

EDUCATION



2017

SPALAH IT-SCHOOL

JavaScript software development

2016-2017

HTMLACADEMY

Web development (HTML & CSS)

2002-2007

NATIONAL MINING UNIVERSITY

Information security of computer systems and networks.